If I've been causing you trouble, I will leave!
如果真的碍到你了 我消失便是
I'M THE VILLAINESS, SO I'M TAMING THE FINAL BOSS!
《因为是反派大小姐》 《所以养了魔王》
"THE VILLAINESS IS ALWAYS CONDEMNED" Are you... Belzebuth?
(反派大小姐总是被谴责) 你是… 佩鲁赛博特吗
Demon King, are you calling my name?
魔王 您叫我的名字吗
I am Keith, Master.
我是吉斯 我的主人
Oh, this won't do.
哎呀 这可不行
The cushion is not positioned correctly.
放置抱枕的角度不对
This tea is not right, too.
这杯茶也不行
I'll make you your usual tea.
我立刻泡杯您常喝的茶
Are you going to break off the engagement with Aileen?
您…打算跟爱琳小姐解除婚约吗
Just do what you want.
解除婚约就解除婚约
However, if Aileen goes missing, it would be a problem.
但要爱琳小姐消失 就太过分了
I don't recall teaching you to hurt women like that.
在下不记得 曾教您如此伤害女性心灵
It's not true.
不是的
I just hope that she doesn't come near me anymore.
我只是希望 她别再靠近我
However, it was conveyed to the demons wrongly, right?
却以错误的方式传达给魔物们是吗
Master. What were you thinking?
我的主人 您是怎么想的
Bel!
佩鲁
There's poison on the shelf. I'm disinfecting it.
柜子里被放了毒药 我正在消毒
Darn humans.
该死的人类
Can you think it through before acting?
你可不可以先经过思考再行动啊
Who cares?
谁管他
Bel. Put out the fire.
佩鲁 把火灭了
Demon King.
魔王
Your orders, please.
请下令
Bring her...
把她…
Bring Aileen Lauren Dautriche to the ball.
把爱琳 罗伦 多德勒带来参加舞会
Are you serious about not going to the ball?
你真的不打算参加舞会吗
I can work for a living.
我能靠工作维生
As long as the engagement is broken off, I won't be punished.
只要被解除婚约 就不会被处刑
I can survive being cut off from the family.
就算被家族断绝关系拒绝往来 也能活下去
Shouldn't you leave the Demon King's Castle as soon as possible then?
那不就应该尽快离开魔王城吗
But, Almond and the rest will cry.
可是 杏仁它们会哭的
They even danced the "Please Don't Leave Me" dance for me.
它们还跳了"不要出走"之舞给我看
Miss Aileen! You have a package.
爱琳小姐 有您的包裹
This is...
这是…
Your gown for the ball the day after tomorrow.
后天舞会穿的礼服
What does this mean?
什么意思
Master has said
我的主人说
to have Aileen put this on at the ball.
让爱琳小姐穿上这套礼服参加舞会
Aileen.
爱琳
Saying all this now...
事到如今说这些也…
I won't go.
我不会去的
He even ordered us to take you there even if you cried, screamed or risked execution.
他还命令说就算你一哭二闹三上吊 也要把你带过去
Even after losing his memory, my Master didn't change.
即便失去记忆 我的主人仍然没变
He will not give up easily on the things he likes.
对于心仪的事物 绝不轻易放手
Things he likes... Why?
心仪的事物 为什么
I slapped him.
我都甩了他一巴掌耶
Demon King must be in love with Miss Aileen.
一定是魔王大人 又喜欢上爱琳小姐了
I... I will never go.
我…我绝对不去
Don't decide so quickly.
别这么快就下决定
Aileen. Here.
爱琳 来
Demon King is calling. Dance.
魔王大人 呼唤之舞
Isaac.
艾札克
Just accept your fate.
你认命吧
He was so cold to me when I seduced him.
当我诱惑他时 他对我那么冷淡
When I've decided to give up, he came after me again.
当我决定放弃时 他又追了上来
I understand that men are hunters by nature,
虽然 男人是以狩猎为生的生物
but this is absolutely unforgivable.
但不可原谅就是不可原谅
I have my principles too.
我也是有坚持的
Master Claude.
库洛德大人
I'll make you...
我会让你…
Regret inviting me to the ball.
后悔招待我来舞会
Why?
为什么
Why is it a duck?
为什么是鸭子
It's because you ordered me to put on this dress
因为您命令我穿着这套礼服
but you didn't order me to show my face.
但没命令我要"露脸"吧
Why are you resisting?
为何要抵抗
This is the most recent trend, duck style.
最近很流行 这种鸭子造型
Impossible.
怎么可能
Take it off.
给我脱掉
No! I can't face Master Claude.
不要 反正我就是 "没脸"见库洛德大人
Master Claude!
库洛德大人
That's just plain stupid!
这样太没常识了
I don't want to be called stupid by a woman with a duck head.
我不想被带着鸭子头套的女性 说自己没常识
Make way.
让路
Why did you take me here?
你突然把我带来这里干嘛
Can I hug you?
我能抱你吗
There's a limit to this.
胡闹也有点限度
I'm about to get angry.
我真的要生气咯
I think I've figured out the strength to hold you.
我好像知道 如何控制抱着你的力气
Keith said, get close to your face and say your name.
吉斯说 靠近你的脸 唤你的名
What did he teach you?
他到底都教了你些什么
What's good doing...
做这种事有什么…
Aileen.
爱琳
I see. Even though you sound tough, you're not used to men's sweet words.
原来如此 虽然你的口气很强硬 但其实你并不习惯男人的甜言蜜语
It seems like I've been fooled.
看来 我被你骗了
That's not true.
没这回事
I... I...
我…我…
Shall we do it again?
要不要再一次
That's so shameless!
太不要脸了吧
Who'd do this before marriage...
哪有人在婚前做这种…
Aileen.
爱琳
I... Love you...
我…爱你…
Love me... You love me...
爱我… 你爱我…
Yes. I love you.
是啊 我爱你
I want to make you cry, comfort you, and spoil you rotten even.
想惹你哭泣 想宠你 甚至是把你宠坏
Are you doing this even after losing memory?
你没记忆了还要走这个路线吗
Whether I've lost my memory does not change my love for you.
无论有没有记忆 我对你的爱似乎完全没变
This must be fate.
这就是命运吧
Do you think you'll be forgiven if you say that now?
你以为这样说 我就会原谅你吗
Yes.
会啊
I really want to cut you down.
我真想斩断这一切
If you can't forgive me as is, then I have an idea.
若说什么都不愿原谅我的话 那就这样吧
Aileen.
爱琳
You can do anything to me. Hit my face or anywhere
你想对我做什么 打我脸或揍我都行
until you feel better.
直到你气消为止
As if I could!
谁办得到啦
Is that so? What a pity.
是哦 好可惜
I was looking forward to what you'd do to me.
我还很期待 你会对我做什么呢
Are you aware that your behaviour now is the complete opposite from before?
你有自觉现在的行为 跟你之前的行为完全相反吗
Love changes a person.
爱会改变一个人
Do you think saying that in a cool way would make me...
你以为一脸帅气地甜言蜜语我就…
All right. I'll forgive you...
好啦 我原谅你就是了…
Then, let's go.
那 我们回去吧
We'll have a dance to announce our relationship.
我们得跳支舞 才能公开表示我们的关系
You should head back first.
你先回去吧
I... I need to fix my makeup.
我…我要补妆
You're already very beautiful.
你现在就已经很美了
I don't want to leave you.
我不想离开你
No way.
那可不行
I'd rather look like a duck
要我这副模样跟你共舞
than dance with you like this.
我还不如变回鸭子
I understand.
我知道了
I'll return to the venue first.
我先回会场吧
As expected of Miss Aileen.
不愧是爱琳小姐
Master Claude fell in love with you again after a slap.
靠一巴掌让库洛德大人重新爱上你
Is... Is that so?
是…是这样吗
I'll get you the lipstick to match this dress.
我去拿搭配礼服的口红
Please wait for me.
请稍等我一下
Master Claude said he loves me.
库洛德大人说 他爱我
You look happy.
您看起来似乎很幸福的样子
Miss Aileen.
爱琳小姐
BELZEBUTH, CV YUKI ONO ONE OF THE DEMON KING'S FOLLOWERS
(佩鲁赛博特 CV小野友树) (魔王的随从之一)
HAS LONG HAIR AND PORCELAIN-LIKE BEAUTY.
(拥有一头长发以及) (如陶瓷般的冷艳美貌)
LOYAL TO DEMON KING CLAUDE AND OBEYS TO THE DEMON KING'S ORDERS.
(对库洛德魔王极为忠诚) (听命于魔王的命令)
A SUPREME DEMON THAT HAS THE ABILITY TO CONTROL OTHER DEMONS.
(是位上级魔物) (且拥有控制其他魔物的能力)
Elephas. What are you trying to do?
艾雷法斯 你想做什么
I don't believe in love, So I wasn't expecting things to head this way.
我不相信爱 所以没想到事情会进展至此…
If this continues, Demon King might regain his memories.
再这样下去 魔王可能会恢复记忆
That would be a problem.
那就麻烦了
In the game, Elephas is the one who helps Demon King regain his memories.
在游戏中 艾雷法斯是 让魔王恢复的角色
This setting had me careless.
因为这个设定让我大意了
You're a charming lord.
你是位很有魅力的主君
I wish I had met you before her.
真希望能在遇到她之前先遇见你
Then, who is your master who is comparable to me?
你那能跟我争艳的主人 是谁呢
She's a monstrous woman.
是个像怪物的女性
It seems like I have to rescue you from prison.
看来 我得拯救被囚困的你了
It's useless.
没用的
Almond?
杏仁
Don't worry. It's still alive.
放心 它还活着
How despicable! How dare you take the demon creatures hostage?
卑鄙 居然拿魔物当人质
They're innocent, foolish creatures.
它们真的是单纯到愚蠢的程度
They didn't even doubt me.
完全不怀疑我
Next, we'll have our actors continue with the play.
接下来 就请演员们继续照剧本走
Actors?
演员
Master Leister. Over here.
列斯塔大人 这里
Miss Aileen has Demon Snuff on her.
爱琳小姐身上有魔香
Miss Aileen, what a shame.
爱琳小姐 真遗憾
Seems like it's just a farce.
看来是一出闹剧
What?
什么
What is happening?
怎么回事
Leister. What is happening?
列斯塔 这是怎么回事
I can't reveal the details
详细情形无法细说
but she intends to summon demons to attack the place.
但她打算让魔物们来攻击会场
Demons?
魔物
No way.
怎么会
She intends to reinstall the Crown Prince as Demon King
她打算让皇太子殿下恢复魔王身份
and have demons rule this country.
让魔物支配这个国家
That's horrible.
太可怕了
Pierre. Let's execute her here at once.
皮耶尔 快点处决她吧
That's right. It cannot be pardoned.
没错 绝不能轻饶
There are other problems too.
还有其他问题
During her time as the fiancee of the Crown Prince,
她明明是皇太子的未婚妻
she had relationships with other men.
却与其他男性有来往
What did you say?
你说什…
All right. If you appreciate the crow's life,
好了 如果你爱惜乌鸦们的命
then don't tell Master Claude the truth.
那就别对库洛德大人说实话
Master Claude. You must know this man.
库洛德大人 您认识这位男性吧
He seemed to have had a night with Aileen.
他似乎曾跟爱琳小姐共度春宵
Master Claude. I'm sorry.
库洛德大人 很抱歉
I... No. We betrayed you.
我… 不 是我们背叛了您
Did you say we...
你说…我们…
What are you saying?
你在说什…
Elephas. You...
艾雷法斯 你…
Calm down.
你冷静点
You can punish me however you like
您要怎么惩罚我都无所谓
but please don't punish Miss Aileen.
不过 请别处决爱琳小姐
Nonsense!
胡说八道
Master Claude. Don't listen to them.
库洛德大人 别相信他们的话
Miss Aileen.
爱琳小姐
You said you were lonely and you wanted me to comfort you.
当时您跟我说很寂寞 要我安慰您
You said you could only rely on me.
说您只能仰赖我的这些话
Were those words merely lies?
都是骗人的吗
Enough!
别说了
Tell me you love me.
跟我说你爱我
Then, I'll believe you.
这样 我就相信你
I should have told him I love him just now.
早知道 刚才就跟他说我爱他了…
Silly.
愚蠢的人
What?
什么
I've been holding back for a long time
至今我一直在忍耐
since you're the Crown Prince.
毕竟你是皇太子嘛
However, I've reached my limit.
不过 我已经到极限了
I feel disgusted being loved by you.
光是被你爱着 就觉得恶心
What do you mean?
你什么意思
This is only natural.
这很正常吧
I'm a human being. How can I have feelings...
我是个人类 怎么可能对魔王…
For a Demon King.
产生爱意呢…
You don't know who you truly are, right?
你不知道自己的真面目吧
You... freak...
你这个…怪物…
That's not true.
不对
Not true, Demon King. Miss Aileen. Lied.
不对 魔王大人 爱琳 骗你
She purposely told a lie...
她故意骗…
Don't disturb.
别来碍事
No way...
不会吧…
This is not true...
这是骗人的吧…
Almond.
杏仁
Master Claude, please stop!
库洛德大人 快住手
Aileen.
爱琳
Master Claude. Did you regain your memories?
库洛德大人 恢复记忆了吗…
Kill her now.
立刻杀了她
She's a traitor who wants to turn my son into a demon.
她是想让我儿子变回魔物的叛徒
Yes!
是
And the demons in the forest. Send the Holy Knights and the troops
还有森林里的魔物 出动圣骑士团和军队
to kill them all!
全都给我讨伐掉
Wait!
等等
Master Claude!
库洛德大人
No. Run now.
不行 趁现在快逃
But.
可是
Miss Aileen.
爱琳小姐
Elephas, kill the little girl!
艾雷法斯 给我杀了那个小姑娘
Run. Aileen...
快逃 爱琳…
Before I return, the demons will...
在我回去之前 魔物们就…
Master Claude!
库洛德大人
Aileen!
爱琳
Aileen. It's the Demon King.
爱琳 是魔王
At that moment, I felt the Demon King's presence.
刚才一瞬间 我感觉到魔王的气息
But, it's strange.
可是 好奇怪
Almond's presence is gone.
杏仁的气息消失了
Almond is with Master Claude
杏仁在库洛德大人身边
so it should be fine.
所以不会有事的
The Holy Knights are coming shortly.
骑士团马上就会过来了
There's no time to waste.
没时间拖拖拉拉的了
Aileen. Pull yourself together.
爱琳 振作点
You want to be the Demon King's wife, don't you?
你想成为魔王的妻子吧
Isaac. Is there a way for all the demons to get away?
艾札克 有方法能让所有魔物都逃走吗
Of course.
当然有
Underground labyrinth.
地下迷宫
Yes. We'll be able to move freely between the castle and the outskirts of the capital.
是的 从城堡到皇都外 全都能自由出入
There are supplies in there too. It should be enough for half a year.
里面也有物资 应该能撑半年吧
Leave it to Doni. The giant moles must be thrilled.
不愧是多尼 大鼹鼠们一定很开心
That's right. Moreover, according to Belzebuth's instructions,
没错 而且按照佩鲁赛博特的指示
I even made it look creepy.
我还特地改造成很诡异的风格
I wasn't expecting you all to build an underground labyrinth.
没想到你们居然建造了地下迷宫
All right, everyone.
好的 各位
I believe you must be feeling uneasy without the Demon King here.
相信大家因魔王不在而感到不安
But from now on, I'll take over Master's duties temporarily.
现在开始 由我暂代主人之职
Some of you may still be confused.
应该还有些人不清楚
The Demon King has bestowed upon me the authority to enforce orders on everyone.
其实魔王曾给我 能对大家下达一次命令的权利
Is that so?
是这样吗
Yes. It's magic that activates when something happens to Master Claude.
是的 当库洛德大人出事时 才能启动的魔法
It's called "Demon King's Deputy".
其名为 "魔王代行"
Everyone. Leave the Demon King's Castle.
各位 离开魔王城
Stay as far away as you can from the human capital.
尽量远离人类的皇都
Amazing.
好强
Don't forget. I'm the right-hand man to Master Claude.
别忘了 我可是库洛德大人的左右手
So, you've become the Demon King again.
没想到你变回魔王了
You're just a supporting character. Aileen is the protagonist.
你只是个配角 爱琳小姐才是主角
What are you saying?
你在说什么
It's still a surprise that there's a character that I can't tame.
居然有我无法攻略的角色
I'm a little amazed by it.
让我有点佩服
No wonder Aileen chose you.
不愧是爱琳小姐的选择
So, Master Claude.
所以 库洛德大人
I will turn you into a princess waiting to be saved.
我要把你变成等待他人拯救的公主
The one who stole my memories... Was it you?
夺走我记忆的人…是你吗
It's a secret.
秘密
It's not good to spoil the story.
暴雷会遭报应的
I never thought we'd have to clear the dungeon.
没想到 我们要攻略迷宫
Are the rest of them who left early with Keith all right?
先行离开的吉斯先生他们 现在还好吗
Don't worry. They should be here to welcome us.
不用担心 他们应该会来迎接
Everyone. Do you know where the point of assembly is?
各位 都知道集合地点在哪吧
If anything happens, that is where...
若发生什么是就在那里…
Order! Order!
传令 传令
Knights are here!
骑马队 来了
Get ready!
快准备 快准备
This is bad. This will...
不妙 这样会…
I'll stay and be the decoy.
我留下来当诱饵吧
I'll be Aileen's decoy and they'll come after me.
我伪装成爱琳小姐 他们就会来追我
No way. You have to run with me.
不可以 你也要跟我一起逃走
Aileen, please meet with the demons.
爱琳小姐请跟魔物们会合
But...
可是…
Isaac.
艾札克先生
I'll leave it to you.
交给你了
Isaac!
艾札克
Don't worry. We will protect her.
放心吧 有我们保护她
I'll go too.
我也去吧
I can speak with the demons. It'll be easier if I am there.
我能与魔物沟通 有我在会比较方便
It'll be fine, Ribbon.
没事的 缎带
All of you...
你们…
Could it be...
难道…
Elephas.
艾雷法斯
Riding on such a big demon
乘坐这么巨大的魔物
makes it easy for me to find you.
让我一下子就找到了
Don't move, all of you.
全部不准动
I'll drop you to your death.
小心我让你们都摔死
All right. Go back to the castle with me.
好了 跟我一起回皇城吧
To hell with it.
谁要听你的
On its own, the Sacred Sword is...
圣剑擅自…